Imagine your life hangs by a thread. Imagine your body
hangs by a wire. Imagine you're not imagining.
Coma is a thriller, mystery film directed by Michael Crichton.
When relatively healthy patients begin having 'complications' during simple operations and ending up in
comas, a concerned doctor defies her male superiors when she suspects a secret plot.
Dr. Susan Wheeler, played by Geneviève Bujold.
Dr. Mark Bellows, played by Michael Douglas.
Mrs. Emerson, played by Elizabeth Ashley.
Dr. George, played by Rip Torn.
Dr. Harris, played by Richard Widmark.
Nancy Greenly, played by Lois Chiles.
Coma is a 1978 American mystery thriller film based on the
1977 novel of the same name by Robin Cook.
The film rights were acquired by director Michael Crichton, who also wrote the screenplay,
and the movie was produced by Martin Erlichmann for Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.
The cast includes Geneviève Bujold, Michael Douglas,
Elizabeth Ashley, Richard Widmark, and Rip Torn.
Among the actors in smaller roles are Tom Selleck, Lois Chiles, and Ed Harris.
The story was adapted again into a two-part television miniseries
broadcast in September 2012 on A&E television network.
The film explores themes of boston, massachusetts, black
market, questioning, desperate, organ trafficking.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.